Guide to the Ron Whyte Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1957-1995; Series II; 72; (72 boxes)
  - Writings of Others
    - Krleža, Miroslav. Kristofor Kolumbo, undated (Box 80)
    - MacLeish, Archibald. Epistle to Be Left in the Earth, undated (Box 80)
    - Magoon, Eaton. Heathen, 1972 (Box 80)
    - Manley, Atwood and Mangum, Margaret Manley. Frederic Remington, undated (Box 80)
    - May, Ted. Augustus B. Frog Makes His Debut, 1988 (Box 80)
    - May, Theodore. Down in the Dumps, 1987 (Box 80)
    - McKuen, Rod. Stanyan Street & Other Sorrows, 1969 December 3 (Box 80)
    - McNeal, Claude. San Francisco Saturday Night, undated (Box 80)
    - Mills, Dale Douglas. Deliver Us from Squid Roe, 1987 July 2; 2 (Box 80)
    - Mosher, Jim. Untitled, undated (Box 80)
    - Newton, Simon. The Nest, 1968 (Box 80)
    - Nodier, Charles. The Crumb Fairy, 1987 June 19 (Box 80)
    - Pintoff, Ernest. Plague, 1968 (Box 81)
    - Reynolds, Jim. Market - Street Man, undated (Box 81)
    - Rosen, Deborah. Wine or Blood..., undated (Box 81)
    - Ryan, Patricia. Equals, 1977 (Box 81)
    - Satuloff, Robert L. Anna's Children, undated; 2 (Box 81)
    - Satuloff, Robert L. Going Against the Grain, 1965, undated; 5 (Box 81)
    - Satuloff, Robert L. Hymn for Deaf Ears, undated (Box 81)
    - Shapiro, Mel. Gabriel Kapuniak, 1961 (Box 81)
    - Sholder, Jack. Outlaws, 1972 (Box 81)
    - Suskin, Steven. Show Tunes, 1983; 4 (Box 81)
    - Soyinka, Wole. A Play of Giants, undated (Box 81)
    - Stevens, George. Lincoln's Doctor's Dog, undated (Box 81)
    - Stuart, Nuba Harold. Exposed Nerve!, 1979 (Box 81)
    - Trustman, Alan R. Bullitt, undated (Box 81)
    - Twain, Mark. Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court, 1972-1978 (Box 81)
      Includes production contract between Ron Whyte and Shanco Productions, Ltd.
    - Wilder, Thornton. Dupont Show of the Month, 1958 January 21 (Box 81)
    - Williams, Tennessee. The Long Goodbye, undated (Box 81)
    - Wolfson, John. Casanova, 1965 (Box 81)
    - Zinsser, David. Benito Cerino, 1968 August 14 (Box 82)
    - Reviews of works by Ron Whyte, 1967-1983; 27 (Box 82)
    - Reviews of works by Ron Whyte, 1967-1983; 29 (Box 83)
- Educational Papers, 1956-1984; Series III; 6.63; (8 boxes)
  Organized by institution.
  Series III consists of educational records, writing assignments, yearbooks, and other material related to Ron Whyte's education.
  - University of Minnesota High School. Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1956-1959, undated; 3 (Box 84)
  - University of Minnesota High School. Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1956-1959; 9 (Box 85)
  - High Point High School yearbook, 1961 (Box 85)
  - Berriman Junior High School yearbook, 1969 (Box 85)
  - Senior Supplement, [1962] (Box 85)
  - Shadle Park High School, 1960; 2 (Box 85)
  - San Francisco State College, 1960, undated; 7 (Box 85)
  - San Francisco State College, 1962-1964, undated; 15 (Box 86)
  - Yale University, 1965, undated; 5 (Box 86)
  - Yale University, 1964-1982, undated; 13 (Box 87)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1974-1975, undated; 7 (Box 87)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1974-1976, undated; 20 (Box 88)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1972-1984, undated; 17 (Box 89)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1974-1976, undated; 26 (Box 90)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1973-1976, undated; 10 (Box 91)
  - Yale New Haven Teachers Institute, undated (Box 91)
- Professional Papers, 1962-1995; Series IV; 6.83; (8 boxes)
  Organized into three subseries: General Professional Papers, Grant Proposals, and Papers of Others.
  Series IV consists of notes, ephemera, copies of printed material, and grant applications associated with Ron Whyte's disability activism and other public service. Also included are professional papers of others.
  - General Professional Papers
    - The Actors Studio, circa 1980-1982; 9 (Box 92)
    - The Actors Studio, 1978-1984, undated; 10 (Box 93)
    - Creative Artists Public Service Program, 1977-1978, undated; 4 (Box 93)
    - The American Book Review, 1978-1985, undated; 6 (Box 93)
    - The Soho Weekly News, 1976-1977, undated; 3 (Box 93)
    - The Soho Weekly News, 1076-1977, undated; 19 (Box 94)
    - National Task Force for Disability and the Arts, 1977-1979, undated; 3 (Box 94)
    - National Task Force for Disability and the Arts, 1978-1983, undated; 31 (Box 95)
    - National Task Force for Disability and the Arts, 1978-1983, undated; 16 (Box 96)
    - National Endowment for the Arts. Advisory Panel, 1983, undated; 4 (Box 96)
    - Religious Communities, The Arts, and The American Revolution Conference, 1975 April 10-11 (Box 96)
  - Grant proposals
    - Cultural Council Foundation - CETA Artists, undated (Box 97)
    - Alternative Lifestyles Inc., 1975 (Box 97)
    - The Llewellyn Miller Fund, 1984-1986, undated; 3 (Box 97)
    - National Cristina Foundation, Inc., 1993-1995; 3 (Box 97)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1982 (Box 97)
    - Religious Communities for the Arts, 1977; 2 (Box 97)
    - The Grantsmanship Center, Los Angeles, 1976-1978, undated; 5 (Box 97)
  - Papers of Others
    - Battcock, Gregory
      - Correspondence, 1963-1979, undated; 7 (Box 97)
      - Financial records, 1973-1978; 2 (Box 97)
      - Androgyny project, 1975, undated; 3 (Box 98)
    - Bradley, William L.
      - Papers, including "A Report on an Inquiry into Current Programs Toward Strengthening the Performance of Board Members of Nonprofit Organizations" by John W. Nason., 1984 (Box 98)
    - Bradley, Paul
      - Unsorted papers, circa 1971-1983; 2 (Box 98)
      - Unsorted papers, circa 1971-1983; 21 (Box 99)
- Subject Files, 1957-1989; Series V; 13; (13 boxes)
  Boxes 100-108: Titles are transcribed from Ron Whyte's original files.
  Series V consists of Ron Whyte's files on topics relating to his research, writing, and activism. Files include notes, copies of printed material, and correspondence.
  - John Calvin Batchelor, 1977 October 10, undated (Box 100)
  - Tom Brezniak, 1977, undated (Box 100)
  - Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 100)
  - Bernardo Bertolucci, 1977, undated (Box 100)
  - Dr. Berlin, undated (Box 100)
  - Leonore Bode, 1977-1978 (Box 100)
  - Book Clubs, 1977 (Box 100)
  - Book of the Month Club, 1977 September 30 (Box 100)
  - Books - SWN -, 1977 June 27, undated (Box 100)
  - Bay Area Rapid Transit Accessible to Disabled, undated (Box 100)
  - Bills: Orthopedic Studio, 1978 May 26 (Box 100)
  - Ordination, 1978 (Box 100)
  - Books to Buy, 1977, undated (Box 100)
  - Books Searches, undated (Box 100)
  - Bunch Festival, [1977] (Box 100)
  - Stuart Byron, 1977 April 4 (Box 100)
  - Riverside Church, 1977, undated (Box 100)
  - Irene Jones - Riverside, 1978 July 11 (Box 100)
  - Statement (Original) Riverside Church, 1978 April 16 (Box 100)
  - Statement Riverside Church, 1978 April 16 (Box 100)
  - The 48th International PEN Congress, New York City 1986 (Box 100)
  - Hugo - Fr. Bookstores, undated (Box 100)
  - Room 78 (empty folder), undated (Box 100)
  - The Interior Distance, undated (Box 100)
  - Accupuncture Assn., undated (Box 100)
  - Hugo - Notre Dame - Articles, undated (Box 100)
  - Hunchback - Makeup - Films, undated (Box 100)
  - Victor Hugo portraits, undated (Box 100)
  - Hugo's Drawings and Dossiers, undated (Box 100)
  - Bibliographies, undated (Box 100)
  - Treasure, undated (Box 100)
  - Victor Hugo portraits, 1980-1981, undated (Box 100)
  - St. Peter's Church, 1974-1975, undated (Box 100)
  - Writer's Guild of America, East Inc., 1985 June 6 (Box 100)
  - Canosa, Whyte, Fischer, Ruff Associates, 1978, undated; 2 (Box 100)
  - Waterman, Getz, Niedelman advertising, 1977hejo, undated (Box 100)
  - Things to File (empty folder), undated (Box 100)
  - Address lists, undated (Box 100)
  - Affiliate Artists, 1977 (Box 100)
  - Tom Allen, 1977 (Box 100)
  - Alta advertising, 1976 April 6 (Box 100)
  - Actors Exp. Unit, 1976 (Box 100)
  - Alter, Herb, undated (Box 100)
  - Alternative Lifestyles, undated (Box 100)
  - American Conservatory Theatre, 1978 (Box 100)
  - Ahlberg, Ralph, 1976-1978 (Box 101)
  - Alper, John, 1977, undated (Box 101)
  - Ken Anger, 1977, undated (Box 101)
  - Avant-Garde Festival, 1978 May 18 (Box 101)
  - Avantgarde Vido, 1977 (Box 101)
  - Babes in Toy-land, undated (Box 101)
  - Sally, Baker, 1978, undated (Box 101)
  - Charles Baker. Selma Hirsher, 1978 July 10 (Box 101)
  - Wind in the Wheat Grass - Jessica Stickney, 1978 (Box 101)
  - Religious Communities for the Arts - Fellowship, 1978, undated (Box 101)
  - Religious Communities for the Arts - Wind in the Wheatgrass, 1978 (Box 101)
  - Religious Communities for the Arts, 1978 (Box 101)
  - Grace originals, 1977-1978, undated (Box 101)
  - Grace of the Handicapped. Carbon, 1978 (Box 101)
  - Abraham Menashe, 1978 January 24 (Box 101)
  - Eliot Fremont-Smith. The Voice, 1978 February 21 (Box 101)
  - Ron Whyte - Papers, 1978, undated (Box 101)
  - Grace of the Handicapped. Xerox, 1978, undated (Box 101)
  - Welfare Hotels, 1977 (Box 101)
  - Welfare Legislation, 1978 (Box 101)
  - SSI + Welfare, 1978-1979 (Box 101)
  - Califano, 1978 March (Box 101)
  - National Assembly News, 1977 September 15 (Box 101)
  - Religious Communities for the Arts (empty folder), undated (Box 101)
  - Religion, 1977 (Box 101)
  - United Church of Christ, 1977, undated (Box 101)
  - Saint Peters, 1977, undated (Box 101)
  - Religion / People, 1978 January 16 (Box 101)
  - Board of Homeland Ministries. Journal of Current Social Issues, 1978 (Box 101)
  - 4th International Congress Art, Religion. San Antonio May 1978, 1978 May (Box 101)
  - Pamela Ilott, 1977, undated (Box 101)
  - CBS news, 1978 (Box 101)
  - Home Attendant (OCIM) / Pam Ilott, 1977-1978 (Box 101)
  - Medicaid (Home Attendant), undated (Box 101)
  - Soyinka, Wole, 1982-1985, undated; 2 (Box 101)
  - Bellamy, Ralph, undated (Box 101)
  - Unsolicited Reviews. Potential, 1975-1976, undated (Box 101)
  - Crown, 1976, undated (Box 101)
  - To Be Filed, 1976 (Box 101)
  - Letters from Publishers, 1975-1976 (Box 101)
  - Publishers' Publicists Association, 1976 January 9 (Box 101)
  - Welcome to Andromeda, 1973 January 30 (Box 101)
  - Visions / PBS, 1977 (Box 101)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1976-1977, undated (Box 101)
  - Soho Stationery, undated (Box 102)
  - Soho Weekly News, 1977 (Box 102)
  - Bills + Receipts, 1976, undated (Box 102)
  - Ellenberg - Soho Weekly News, 1977, undated (Box 102)
  - Ron Melville Whyte. Stationery - Formal, undated (Box 102)
  - Dance L, undated (Box 102)
  - Stationery - Brandeis, undated (Box 102)
  - John Stix - Director, 1978 July 10 (Box 102)
  - The Stuart Ostrow Foundation Inc., undated (Box 102)
  - Telephone, undated (Box 102)
  - Telegrams, 1977 October 5 (Box 102)
  - Terrorists, 1977-1978 (Box 102)
  - Theatre / General, 1977 (Box 102)
  - Theatre Communications Group, undated (Box 102)
  - Theater Essays, 1977 November 10 (Box 102)
  - Transexuals + Transvestites, 1975, undated (Box 102)
  - Williams, Tennessee, 1977-1978, undated (Box 102)
  - Ron Whyte: Resume, undated (Box 102)
  - Resumé / Ron Whyte C. V., undated (Box 102)
  - Wright, Charles, undated (Box 102)
  - Yale Divinity Sc. Project, 1977 (Box 102)
  - Yale Record, 1966 September (Box 102)
  - Bob, Young, undated (Box 102)
  - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, 1977-1988 (Box 102)
  - Leonard Peters, undated (Box 102)
  - P. R. Originals, 1976, undated (Box 102)
  - Paul Castiglione, 1977, undated (Box 102)
  - Poets + Writers Inc. CODA, 1977-1978 (Box 102)
  - Politics (empty folder), undated (Box 102)
  - Press releases, 1976 (Box 102)
  - Programs, 1971, undated (Box 102)
  - P. E. N., 1977, undated (Box 102)
  - Publishers' Publicists Association, 1977 July 27 (Box 102)
  - Publishers Weekly. Interviews / Articles (empty folder), undated (Box 102)
  - Radio City Music Hall, 1978 (Box 102)
  - Radio Records, 1977 (Box 102)
  - Richards, Stanley, 1976 November 21 (Box 102)
  - Kenneth Rider, 1977-1978, undated (Box 102)
  - Roeger, George, undated (Box 102)
  - Lewis Rosen (text), undated (Box 102)
  - Rolling Stone Stationery, undated (Box 102)
  - Ted Solotaroff (the American Review), undated (Box 102)
  - Sci-Fi - Comix, 1976 (Box 102)
  - Scientology, 1977, undated (Box 102)
  - Sermonettes / Related materials, 1977 July 22 (Box 102)
  - Bills - Soho Weekly News, 1976 (Box 102)
  - Shelter West, undated (Box 102)
  - Gary Sharnhorst. Purdue University, 1976 January 12 (Box 102)
  - Shirley Soffer (Bowker), 1977 November 22 (Box 102)
  - S. S. I., undated (Box 102)
  - Scratch + Sniff, 1977 (Box 102)
  - Chris Sergal (empty folder), undated (Box 102)
  - Scripts - London Play Exchange, undated (Box 102)
  - The Voice envelope, 1984 November 30 (Box 102)
  - Braziller, 1976 (Box 102)
  - Mel Marvin - Non-Whyte Shows, 1978 March 31 (Box 102)
  - Greenwich Village - East Village - Bowery, 1977 November 28 (Box 102)
  - Lyrics - Whyte, Satuloff, Marvin (empty folder), undated (Box 102)
  - NYC, 1981 (Box 102)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1984-1987 (Box 102)
  - Gnu Theatre, undated (Box 102)
  - Canosa, Whyte, Fischer + Ruff Associates, undated (Box 102)
  - Canosa, Whyte, Fischer, Ruff. Receipts Paid, 1978 (Box 102)
  - Address Lists, 1978, undated (Box 102)
  - Canosa, Whyte, Fischer, + Ruff Associates, 1977, undated; 3 (Box 102)
  - Disability, undated (Box 102)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) - Pay receipts, 1977-1978, undated; 2 (Box 103)
  - G. Culver. Actors Studio, 1978 July 10 (Box 103)
  - Joe Larry Cook (empty folder), undated (Box 103)
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade, 1977, undated (Box 103)
  - Chelsea Theater Center, 1977 (Box 103)
  - Sally Champlin, 1970 December 14 (Box 103)
  - Coordination Council of Literary Magazines, 1972-1977 (Box 103)
  - Labor Publ. Inc. (empty folder), undated (Box 103)
  - Omega + Press Releases, undated (Box 103)
  - Catalogs sent - Lists (empty folder), undated (Box 103)
  - Creative Artists Public Service Program grant material, 1977-1978 (Box 103)
  - Anderson Clark, 1977-1978 (Box 103)
  - Joe Carliner, 1978 February 10, undated (Box 103)
  - 4th International Conference, 1978 (Box 103)
  - General Legislative, 1977-1978 (Box 103)
  - Ted Gill, 1977-1978 (Box 103)
  - Goldstein Stationery, undated (Box 103)
  - Grants, 1977-1978 (Box 103)
  - Gray Panthers (empty folder), undated (Box 103)
  - Charlie Haid, undated (Box 103)
  - James Hall / 87 Christopher NYC 10014, 1978, undated (Box 103)
  - Abby Hirsh, 1978 May (Box 103)
  - House - Miscellaneous (Where to get), undated (Box 103)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1977 November 22 (Box 103)
  - Journal of Popular Culture of Film, 1977 September 29 (Box 103)
  - Larry Jurrist, 1973 (Box 103)
  - Bill Kohler, 1977-1978 (Box 103)
  - Kurt Konrad, 1977 (Box 103)
  - Kropf, 1976, undated (Box 103)
  - Gays, 1977-1978, undated (Box 103)
  - Eric Ruff - Empire State College, 1976-1978, undated (Box 103)
  - Nelson Dos Santos. Tereza Batista, undated (Box 103)
  - Mary Worth, 1977-1978 (Box 103)
  - Julie Nixon Eisenhower, 1977 (Box 103)
  - Empire State - Erik Ruff, 1978 August 1978 (Box 103)
  - M. Dana, undated (Box 103)
  - Nelson Dos Santos, 1977, undated (Box 103)
  - Dover - Notes on Articles, undated (Box 103)
  - Letters [carbon], 1973 (Box 103)
  - Liturgy and the Arts, 1977 (Box 103)
  - Louisville. Joint Office of Worship, 1976 September 15-19 (Box 103)
  - Messenger Receipts, 1977 (Box 103)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club, undated (Box 103)
  - Martha, undated (Box 103)
  - Mel Marvin, undated (Box 103)
  - Omega One: copied reviews, undated (Box 103)
  - Castaways, 1977 February 11 (Box 103)
  - Wrong Turn on the Yellow Brick Road, undated (Box 103)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1984 March 31 (Box 103)
  - Mitsui, 1978-1979, undated (Box 103)
  - Deborah Jowitt, 1984 April 10 (Box 103)
  - Language / Theory / Propaganda, 1984 April (Box 103)
  - On Language - Safire, William, 1984 (Box 103)
  - Magazine Jobs, 1977-1978, undated (Box 103)
  - Mark Twain - rare, undated (Box 103)
  - Stage Reviews - The Washington Post, 1984 April 13 (Box 104)
  - Theatre Reviews - Village Voice, 1984-1989 (Box 104)
  - Television = Reviews, 1984 (Box 104)
  - Sarris, Andrew - clips, 1984 (Box 104)
  - Simenon, Georges, 1984 April 22 (Box 104)
  - Strasberg, Lee, 1983 October 27, undated (Box 104)
  - Ron Whyte, 1978 November 6 (Box 104)
  - Haiku - New York, 1969, undated (Box 104)
  - Notes + Fragments, 1977, undated (Box 104)
  - Notes + Fragments - File under: (Writing), 1977, undated (Box 104)
  - Plot Ideas, 1977 (Box 104)
  - Sermons, undated (Box 104)
  - Ron Whyte's parents, 1977-1978 (Box 104)
  - Ron Whyte - Photos, 1973 (Box 104)
  - Wrong Turn / Louise Photos, undated (Box 104)
  - Union Theological Seminary: Course Evaluations, 1976 (Box 104)
  - Medicare, 1977 (Box 104)
  - Mag Jobs, 1977 (Box 104)
  - Home Health Aid, 1976 (Box 104)
  - Finances, undated (Box 104)
  - Drama Guild, 1977-1978 (Box 104)
  - File: Found Poems, 1984 (Box 104)
  - Chaffey Ed - UTS 1983 -, 1984 May 17 (Box 104)
  - Income Tax Return of Fabiano Canosa, 1983 (Box 104)
  - Gerald Chapman, 1984 (Box 104)
  - The New York Times - Critics' Choices, undated (Box 104)
  - Harold Clurman, undated (Box 104)
  - National Task Force for Disability and the Arts, undated (Box 104)
  - Article on Biddle - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978 (Box 104)
  - Chronological File - Correspondence, 1978 December 21 (Box 104)
  - Home Again, Home Again, undated (Box 104)
  - National Endowment for the Arts / Disability, 1977-1978 (Box 104)
  - 504 Task Force. National Endowment for the Arts, 1978 March 7 (Box 104)
  - Dr. Friedman, Nassau County Medical Center, 1978 (Box 104)
  - Mrs. Rutman / Office of Vocational Rehabilitation, 1977-1978 (Box 104)
  - 504 Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box 104)
  - Walter F. Anderson. National Endowment for the Arts - Music, 1978 July 5 (Box 104)
  - John Jay - Crisis File, 1978 (Box 104)
  - Jory Graham & Cancer, 1977-1980 (Box 104)
  - Receipts / XEROX - printing, 1978, undated (Box 104)
  - Receipts / Other, 1977-1978 (Box 104)
  - Receipts / Postage, 1978 (Box 104)
  - Henry Holden, 1977-1978 (Box 104)
  - National Task Force Prospectus' Conception (empty folder), undated (Box 104)
  - Contracts (empty folder), undated (Box 104)
  - Cable, T. V. Info, undated (Box 104)
  - Posthus Theatret, 1974-1977 (Box 104)
  - Interviews / Originals, 1974 (Box 104)
  - Correspondence File, 1978; 3 (Box 104)
  - National Arts & The Handicapped Information Service, undated; 3 (Box 104)
  - Quasimodo, 1979 (Box 104)
  - Schools (empty folder), undated (Box 104)
  - Vendorizing, 1977 (Box 104)
  - Ordination - Irene Jones, 1978 (Box 104)
  - Dorianne Beyer, 1977 August 25 (Box 104)
  - Passport, undated (Box 104)
  - Loans: Academic Financial Services, 1977, undated (Box 104)
  - Receipts, 1977-1978 (Box 105)
  - 1979 Foundation Inquiries (Box 105)
  - Mimi, 1971-1976 (Box 105)
  - Access / Design, 1977 (Box 105)
  - Access / Legislative, 1977 (Box 105)
  - Access / Travel, 1977 (Box 105)
  - Art / Exhibits & Shows (empty folder), undated (Box 105)
  - Artists / General, 1977 November 4 (Box 105)
  - Art / Concerts - Music (empty folder), undated (Box 105)
  - Art / Theatre, 1977-1978 (Box 105)
  - Attitudes, Prejudice, Exploitation, 1977-1978 (Box 105)
  - Education by, undated (Box 105)
  - Education of, undated (Box 105)
  - Disability: Cases / Success, 1976-1978 (Box 105)
  - Disability / Cases - Tragedy, 1977-1978 (Box 105)
  - Disability / Organizations, 1977 September 2 (Box 105)
  - Disability / Publications (empty folder), undated (Box 105)
  - Disability / Religion, 1978 January 1 (Box 105)
  - Access / Architecture, undated (Box 105)
  - Access / Communication (empty folder), undated (Box 105)
  - Access / Design ( empty folder), undated (Box 105)
  - Access / Transportation, undated (Box 105)
  - Introduction: Grace of the Handicapped, undated (Box 105)
  - Horatio / St. Louis. Original, 1971, undated (Box 105)
  - Bills & Receipts, 1978 (Box 105)
  - From: Ron B-W. To: Paul B-W. Re: Clippings, 1979 (Box 105)
  - Masters: for xerox & offsets, 1978, undated (Box 105)
  - Ron Whyte contracts, 1979 August 21 (Box 105)
  - Empire State College. Intern Program, etc., 1979, undated (Box 105)
  - Mattel, 1976, undated (Box 105)
  - Access / Architecture, 1977-1978 (Box 105)
  - World Book Encyclopedia, 1970-1973 (Box 105)
  - Wilcock, 1976, undated (Box 105)
  - World Book, 1976-1978 (Box 105)
  - Kostelanetz, 1972-1973 (Box 105)
  - Biographical notes, undated (Box 105)
  - Resumés, undated (Box 105)
  - Journal-California. B. Johnson, 1979-1980 (Box 105)
  - Lennon / Ono, 1972 March 30 (Box 105)
  - John Wilcock, 1978-1979 (Box 105)
  - World Book, 1979-1980 (Box 105)
  - Gay & Miscellaneous, undated (Box 105)
  - Loose in Files, 1980 (Box 105)
  - Grants, 1977-1979; 2 (Box 105)
  - New York Book Fair, 1976 (Box 105)
  - H. P. Lovecraft, undated (Box 105)
    Includes 1 audiocassette
    Conditions Governing Access
    Use of original audiocassette is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 105)
  - Alternative Lifestyle, Inc. grant proposal, 1974, undated (Box 105)
  - Shakers, 1982 September -October (Box 105)
  - Disability - Washington Dec. '78. Miscellaneous File, 1978 December (Box 106)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1972-1975 (Box 106)
  - New Dramatists File, 1983 (Box 106)
  - Arena, 1981 March 20 (Box 106)
  - Medical, 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - September 1978, 1980-1984, undated (Box 106)
  - Private Correspondence. Arena Stage, 1974 May 20 (Box 106)
  - Hunchback - Music, 1970-1979, undated (Box 106)
  - Foundation Center, 1976, undated; 2 (Box 106)
  - Education, 1977 December 11 (Box 106)
  - Fundraising Schemes, 1977-1978 (Box 106)
  - Government Legislation (empty folder), undated (Box 106)
  - Incorporation Papers, 1977, undated (Box 106)
  - National Task Force. Legal Documents, 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - National Task Force. Grant Proposals, undated (Box 106)
  - Media / Television / Radio, undated (Box 106)
  - Media, 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - NTDA Stationery, undated (Box 106)
  - Task Forces. Finances (empty folder), undated (Box 106)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare. Thelma Schmones, 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - Leonore Hudson, undated (Box 106)
  - Fundraising. National Task Force, 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - Fundraising. National Task Force (continued), 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - National Task Force. Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box 106)
  - 1st Board Meeting. National Task Force, 1978 January 30 (Box 106)
  - National Task Force. Fragments, 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - Task Force - Letters, 1978 (Box 106)
  - May 9, 1978 Meeting, 1978 May 9 (Box 106)
  - Pace University - Work study contracts, 1978, undated (Box 106)
  - National Task Force. Board Meeting. September 22, 1978, 1978 September 22 (Box 106)
  - Andromeda clips, undated (Box 106)
  - 1969 - St. Suter Project (Box 106)
  - Ron Whyte / Past Reviews, 1973-1977 (Box 106)
  - Ron Whyte Bio '79, [1979] (Box 106)
  - Union Theological Seminary - Ron Whyte, Alternative Lifestyles, Inc., 1975 (Box 106)
  - Allen J. Hubin, undated (Box 106)
  - Samuel French, Inc., 1984 September 4 (Box 106)
  - Lee McClure, 1983-1985, undated; 2 (Box 106)
  - Ron Whyte / Credits, 1977-1978 (Box 107)
  - Kenneth Anger, 1975-1977, undated (Box 107)
  - Rosenstone, Howard, 1977-1978 (Box 107)
  - Hugo articles, 1969, undated; 11 (Box 107)
  - Arts / Theatre, 1977 (Box 107)
  - Arts / Film - Video, undated (Box 107)
  - Arts / Television, 1978 (Box 107)
  - Common Ground, 1964-1973, undated; 2 (Box 107)
  - American Book Review article on movie novelization, 1983, undated (Box 107)
  - American Book Review - Theater and Film, undated (Box 107)
  - Posthus Teatret, 1976-1978 (Box 107)